like I mentioned I do live in Seattle
which is a good place to be kind of
gluten-free and kind of crunchy and such
we uh crunchy it's good word it you we
we like our healthy food we don't have a
lot of uh we have a lot of rain not a
lot of sun
obviously I'm starting to the point
where I just don't even like the sun
anymore because I never tan that like
that would be great if that could happen
I just go white burn peel that's all
that's all that I get and know a sunburn
more than anything now is it's just
embarrassing cuz I feel like when you
have a sunburn it's basically just
wearing a sign around your neck that
says hey I I have no idea how the Sun
Works 35 years later big ball light co-
figure
I and I'm glad I'm married cuz it's hard
to pick up on ladies when you're peeling
and you basically have the last form of
leprosy left on the planet be like hey
where you going here take a piece of me
with you
Sun seems to take people by surprise up
in the Seattle area I can't tell you how
many times at the beginning of the
summer people will come up to you and
start conversations being like hey it's
staying light so much
later have you noticed that like it's
been getting dark at 9:15 and then like
2 weeks ago it was getting dark at
8:45 I'm like well yeah this happened
last year you know I had a friend of
mine come up to me the other day he's
like dude this sucks I guess boating
season's almost over I like well you
obviously have much more money than I do
I have never I've never noticed boating
season really I don't I don't even know
what boating season is to be honest I
don't know if you stop hunting them at
some point or if they're under 20 ft you
throw it back I don't
know I would like to have a boat that
sounds nice there are people a lot of
money up in Seattle now with Amazon and
Microsoft people are getting big boats
getting yachts
uh I was recently introduced to the term
mega yacht somebody had parked one off
the shore of Seattle it was a mega yacht
that was worth $110
million right you can't even wrap your
brain around that however I think the
most fascinating part of it was that
just to fill it with fuel costs
$400,000 right cuz I i' I've been on a
boat before when it's pulled up to like
one of those little gas docks you can't
do that with that sort of pull up there
hey what's up how's it going man cool
you got
gas sweet I'm going to need all your
gas all it do you have friends with gas
call them too I'm going to need all the
gas you have do I press debit how does
this work it's just it's $400,000 you
can't negotiate I have gold will you
take gold I just just have a big bag of
gold that's what I you don't take gold
but you take Discover that's weird okay
I feel like half the appeal of getting a
boat is just coming up with the cool
name to go with it and I feel like
especially with yachts and sailboats
they always have these really rich
sounding names always things like loving
life ain't things
Grand that's cool I want to try that
with my car just yeah everybody pile
into this should have tried harder
that's
mine should have tried harder too
actually last car was stolen